questions = [
    { answer: "Afghanistan", question: "Three equal vertical bands of black, red and green. There is a mosque with flags either side in the center of the flag." },
    { answer: "Albania", question: "Red with a black two-headed eagle in the center." },
    { answer: "Algeria", question: "Two equal vertical bands of green and white. There is a red crescent with a five pointed start in the center of the flag." },
    { answer: "Andorra", question: "Three vertical bands of blue, yellow and red, with the national coat of arms in the center. The coat of arms features a quartered shield with the motto 'Virtus Unita Fortior' underneath." },
    { answer: "Angola", question: "Two equal horizontal bands of red and black, with a centered yellow emblem consisting of a five-pointed star within half a cogwheel crossed by a machete." },
    { answer: "Argentina", question: "Three horizontal bands of sky blue, white and sky blue. In the center is a radiant yellow sun with a human face known as the sun of may." },
    { answer: "Armenia", question: "Three equal horizontal bands of red, blue and orange." },
    { answer: "Australia", question: "Blue with the union jack in the top left. There are 5 stars to the right of the union jack and 1 star underneath it." },
    { answer: "Austria", question: "Three equal horizontal bands of red, white and red." },
    { answer: "Azerbaijan", question: "Three equal horizontal bands of sky blue, red and green. There is a white vertical crescent moon and an eight-pointed star in the center." },
    { answer: "Bangladesh", question: "Green with a large red circle in the center." },
    { answer: "Barbados", question: "three equal vertical bands of blue, gold, and blue. With the head of a black trident centered on the gold band." },
    { answer: "Belarus", question: "red horizontal band and green horizontal band. A white vertical stripe on the left side bears a national ornamentation." },
    { answer: "Belgium", question: "three equal vertical bands of black, yellow, and red." },
    { answer: "Benin", question: "two equal horizontal bands of yellow and red with a vertical green band on the left side." },
    { answer: "Botswana", question: "light blue with a horizontal white-edged black stripe in the center." },
    { answer: "Brazil", question: "green with a large yellow diamond in the center bearing a blue celestial globe with 27 white five-pointed stars." },
    { answer: "Bulgaria", question: "Three equal horizontal bands of white, green, and red." },
    { answer: "Cambodia", question: "three horizontal bands of blue, red, and blue with a white three-towered temple representing Angkor Wat in the center of the red band." },
    { answer: "Cameroon", question: "three equal vertical bands of green, red, and yellow, with a yellow five-pointed star centered in the red band." },
    { answer: "Canada", question: "two vertical bands of red with a white square between them. An 11-pointed red maple leaf is centered in the white square." },
    { answer: "Chad", question: "three equal vertical bands of blue, yellow, and red." },
    { answer: "Chile", question: "two equal horizontal bands of white and red. There is a blue square at the top left. The square bears a white five-pointed star." },
    { answer: "China", question: "red with a large yellow five-pointed star and four smaller yellow five-pointed stars." },
    { answer: "Colombia", question: "three horizontal bands of yellow, blue, and red." },
    { answer: "Cuba", question: "five equal horizontal bands of blue alternating with white. A red equilateral triangle based on the left side bears a white, five-pointed star in the center." },
    { answer: "Cyprus", question: "white with a copper-colored silhouette of an island above two green crossed olive branches in the center of the flag." },
    { answer: "Czech Republic", question: "two equal horizontal bands of white and red with a blue isosceles triangle based on the left side." },
    { answer: "Denmark", question: "red with a white cross that extends to the edges of the flag." },
    { answer: "Ecuador", question: "three horizontal bands of yellow, blue, and red with the coat of arms superimposed at the center of the flag." },
    { answer: "Egypt", question: "three equal horizontal bands of red, white, and black. The gold Eagle of Saladin is centered in the white band." },
    { answer: "Estonia", question: "three equal horizontal bands of blue, black, and white." },
    { answer: "Ethiopia", question: "three equal horizontal bands of green, yellow, and red, with a yellow pentagram centered on the three bands." },
    { answer: "Finland", question: "white with a blue cross extending to the edges of the flag." },
    { answer: "France", question: "three equal vertical bands of blue, white, and red." },
    { answer: "Gabon", question: "three equal horizontal bands of green, yellow, and blue." },
    { answer: "Georgia", question: "white rectangle with a central red cross extending to all four sides of the flag. Each of the four quadrants displays a small red cross." },
    { answer: "Germany", question: "three equal horizontal bands of black, red, and gold." },
    { answer: "Ghana", question: "three equal horizontal bands of red, yellow, and green, with a large black five-pointed star centered in the yellow band." },
    { answer: "Gibraltar", question: "two horizontal bands of white and red with a three-towered red castle in the center of the white band. Hanging from the castle gate is a gold key centered in the red band." },
    { answer: "Greece", question: "Nine equal horizontal stripes of blue alternating with white. A blue square bearing a white cross appears in the upper left corner." },
    { answer: "Guinea", question: "three equal vertical bands of red, yellow, and green." },
    { answer: "Honduras", question: "three equal horizontal bands of blue, white, and blue, with five blue, five-pointed stars arranged in an X pattern centered in the white band." },
    { answer: "Hong Kong", question: "red with a stylized, white, five-petal Bauhinia flower in the center." },
    { answer: "Hungary", question: "three equal horizontal bands of red, white, and green." },
    { answer: "Iceland", question: "blue with a red cross outlined in white extending to the edges of the flag." },
    { answer: "India", question: "three equal horizontal bands of subdued orange, white, and green, with a blue chakra centered in the white band." },
    { answer: "Ireland", question: "three equal vertical bands of green, white, and orange." },
    { answer: "Isle of Man", question: "red with the Three Legs of Man emblem, in the center." },
    { answer: "Israel", question: "white with a blue six-pointed linear star centered between two equal horizontal blue bands near the top and bottom edges of the flag." },
    { answer: "Italy", question: "three equal vertical bands of green, white, and red" },
    { answer: "Jamaica", question: "diagonal yellow cross divides the flag into four triangles that are green and black." },
    { answer: "Japan", question: "white with a large red disk in the center" },
    { answer: "Kenya", question: "three equal horizontal bands of black, red, and green. The red band is edged in white and a large Maasai warrior's shield is superimposed at the center." },
    { answer: "North Korea", question: "three horizontal bands of blue, red, and blue. The red band is edged in white. On the left side of the red band is a white disk with a red five-pointed star." },
    { answer: "South Korea", question: "white with a red and blue yin-yang symbol in the center. There is a black trigram in each corner of the white field." },
    { answer: "Latvia", question: "three horizontal bands of maroon, white, and maroon." },
    { answer: "Lebanon", question: "three horizontal bands consisting of red, white, and red with a green cedar tree centered in the white band." },
    { answer: "Liberia", question: "11 equal horizontal stripes of red alternating with white. A white five-pointed star appears on a blue square in the upper left corner." },
    { answer: "Lithuania", question: "three equal horizontal bands of yellow, green, and red." },
    { answer: "Luxembourg", question: "three equal horizontal bands of red, white, and light blue." },
    { answer: "Macedonia", question: "a yellow sun with eight broadening rays extending to the edges of the red field." },
    { answer: "Madagascar", question: "two equal horizontal bands of red and green with a vertical white band of the same width on left side." },
    { answer: "Malawi", question: "three equal horizontal bands of black, red, and green with a radiant, rising, red sun centered on the black band." },
    { answer: "Mali", question: "three equal vertical bands of green, yellow, and red" },
    { answer: "Malta", question: "two equal vertical bands of white and red. In the upper left corner is a representation of the George Cross." },
    { answer: "Mexico", question: "three equal vertical bands of green, white, and red. There's a coat of arms is centered in the white band." },
    { answer: "Morocco", question: "red with a green pentacle known as Solomon's seal in the center of the flag." },
    { answer: "Netherlands", question: "three equal horizontal bands of red, white, and blue." },
    { answer: "New Zealand", question: "Blue with the union jack in the top left. There are 4 stars to the right of the union jack." },
    { answer: "Nigeria", question: "Three equal vertical bands of green, white, and green." },
    { answer: "Norway", question: "Red with a blue cross outlined in white that extends to the edges of the flag." },
    { answer: "Pakistan", question: "Green with a vertical white band on the left side. A large white crescent and star are centered in the green field." },
    { answer: "Poland", question: "Two equal horizontal bands of white and red." },
    { answer: "Portugal", question: "two vertical bands of green and red with the national coat of arms centered on the dividing line." },
    { answer: "Qatar", question: "Maroon with a broad white serrated band on the left side." },
    { answer: "Romania", question: "Three equal vertical bands of blue, yellow, and red." },
    { answer: "Russia", question: "Three equal horizontal bands of white, blue, and red." },
    { answer: "Senegal", question: "Three equal vertical bands of green, yellow, and red with a small green five-pointed star centered in the yellow band." },
    { answer: "Singapore", question: "Two equal horizontal bands of red and white. Near the left side of the red band, there is a vertical, white crescent partially enclosing five white five-pointed stars arranged in a circle." },
    { answer: "Somalia", question: "Light blue with a large white five-pointed star in the center." },
    { answer: "South Africa", question: "Two equal width horizontal bands of red and blue separated by a central green band that splits into a horizontal Y. The Y embraces a black isosceles triangle." },
    { answer: "Spain", question: "Three horizontal bands of red, yellow, and red with the national coat of arms on the left side of the yellow band." },
    { answer: "Swaziland", question: "Three horizontal bands of blue, red, and blue. Centered in the red band is a large black and white shield." },
    { answer: "Sweden", question: "Blue with a golden yellow cross extending to the edges of the flag." },
    { answer: "Switzerland", question: "Red square with a bold, equilateral white cross in the center that does not extend to the edges of the flag." },
    { answer: "Tunisia", question: "Red with a white disk in the center bearing a red crescent nearly encircling a red five-pointed star." },
    { answer: "Turkey", question: "Red with a vertical white crescent moon and white five-pointed star centered just outside the crescent opening." },
    { answer: "Ukraine", question: "Two equal horizontal bands of light blue and yellow." },
    { answer: "United Kingdom", question: "Blue field with a red cross in the center. The cross has four red lines that run from the center of the cross to each corner of the flag. The red cross and lines are edged in white." },
    { answer: "United States", question: "13 equal horizontal stripes of red alternating with white. There is a blue rectangle in the upper left corner bearing 50 small, white, five-pointed stars." },
    { answer: "Uruguay", question: "Nine equal horizontal stripes of white alternating with blue. A white square in the upper hoist-side corner with a yellow sun bearing a human face known as the Sun of May." }
];

module.exports = {
    questions
};